YUGANDHAR BUDHA

"Dedicated and passionate **Computer Science educator** with one year of experience teaching at a coaching center in my town in west Bengal, striving to bridge the gap between theory and practical application. While maintaining a full-time role at iCIMS as Associate analyst, I am committed to sharing my expertise, fostering curiosity, and empowering students with **essential technical skills, placement guidance** Seeking opportunities to enhance learning experiences".

LANGUAGES

- English
- Telugu
- Bengali
- Hindi

SKILLS

- Java Using OOP's
- Core Java
- C, Python
- SQL, RDBMS
- Data Structures
- Front-End: HTML, CSS and Java script
- Frameworks: Tailwind and Bootstrap
- Ticketing Tools: | IRA and Salesforce.

CONTACT:

- 8250421321/7602799199
- Yugandharb151@yahoo.com
- LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/yugandhar-b-a37148222/utm_source=share&utm_campaign=share_via&utm_content=profile&utm_medium=ios_app

EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER 2024- PRESENT

Getting to learn lot of skills in this project and with our product (icims) I am getting challenges every day and learning every day.

Technologies like HTML, CSS, Basic JS scripts and SQL are my daily basis work and tools like **Salesforce**, **Workday and JIRA**, etc. In my present job our client #iCIMS (Product) has gave me opportunity to work with their clients to resolve issues in platforms like JIRA, Salesforce with editing and designing (UI/UX), ICIMS web portals, IFORMS, Branding of the client-side portals etc.

2022-2024

ASSOCIATE ANALYST

Received multiple **client appreciations**, completed front-end zero to hero training and Gained quality knowledge from this project in **GlobalLogic.**

EDUCATION

MCA, ADITYA COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING 2020-2022
AND TECHNOLOGY, SURAMPALEM

BSC, IDEAL COLLEGE OF ARTS AND 2017-2020 SCIENCES, KAKINADA

ACHIEVEMENTS

Received best performer from placements co-ordination cell. Received multiple client appreciations in iCIMS.

Played university level cricket while pursuing my graduation.